https://www.webchick.com/privacy_policy.htm

PRIVACY POLICY
Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.Personal Information You Choose to Provide / Registration InformationYou will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you contract us to perform design or programming, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts.Web Site Use InformationSimilar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.What Are Cookies?A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.How Do We Protect Your Information?How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. Certain DisclosuresWe may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Site, the users of the Site, and/or our Affiliated Parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of the Site, us, or third parties.Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is not longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Your ConsentBy using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
CONTACT US
Web Chick®Email: Crissy@WebChick.comPhone: 740-681-1769
CENTRAL OHIO WEB DESIGNERSOFFERING UNLIMITED UPDATESALL COMPLETED WITHIN24 HOURS DAILYVIEW OUR PORTFOLIO
Web Chick ®   Located in Central Ohiocopyright 1998-2020WebChick.com, CentralOhioWebDesigners.com Privacy Policy
